(Mrs Cooper:)That's not funny.
(Mrs Cooper:)Maybe we should sit at the table.
Well, I'm sure that you
have a lot of questions.
(Sheldon:)Who was he?
(Mrs Cooper:)His name is Ron.
I met him at my prayer group.
(Sheldon:)How long have you been
involved with him?
(Mrs Cooper:)A few months.
(Sheldon:)And of those few months,
(Sheldon:)how long have you been
a demented sex pervert?
(Mrs Cooper:)That is no way
to speak to your mother.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps not.
(Sheldon:)But it is a way to speak
to a woman who quoted the Bible
(Sheldon:)to me my whole life,
and then desecrates
(Sheldon:)one of Ethan Allen's finest sofas.
(Mrs Cooper:)I will give you one opportunity,
young man, to apologize.
(Sheldon:)-Or what?
-Or I will send you to your room.